Ana Chkhaidze: Okay, thank you. Mike is responsible. Bye.
Ana Chkhaidze: I remember. Is that
Ana Chkhaidze: a lot of it was when I made my eyes like unfocused. I saw a lot of like different patterns, and like different, like
Ana Chkhaidze: pretty much circles on the screen. And I don't know because the mouse was on the screen, so I don't know if that was like kind of like. Why, we were like a lot of like main points on that mouse.
Ana Chkhaidze: But when I would notice was like on the top right of the screen, I would notice, like there would be a circle, and then it would like gradually get bigger. It happened a lot with that one where, like there were circles like some point in the screen, like either, it was like
Ana Chkhaidze: Like a half circle, or like just like a circle that was just gradually getting bigger.
Ana Chkhaidze: I also noticed there was like spirals. A lot of the spirals were like, made up of like smaller circles that would just like be in a spiral
Ana Chkhaidze: other times. It was just like kind of like being hypnotized. And it was just like a like a swirl just in the middle of the screen.
Ana Chkhaidze: also remember, like there were some patterns I remember there were like squiggly, like very thin, squiggly lines like down going down the screen.
Ana Chkhaidze: And
Ana Chkhaidze: There were like a lot. But I don't recall there's a lot of pattern, a lot of like swirls, a lot of mainly circles, I would say, either like in the corner of the screen, or there would be like 2 circles at once on either side of the screen, and it would just like be gradually getting bigger. I didn't notice anything like gradually getting smaller, though I don't know if I missed it, or like
Ana Chkhaidze: I'm just making it up in my head that everything just gets bigger and nothing gets smaller but I just noticed like spirals getting bigger or like the circle, like, just gradually, like pumping and getting bigger. So yeah, I didn't witness anything getting smaller.
Ana Chkhaidze: I think that's it. I'm trying to recall if there's anything else.
Ana Chkhaidze: But yeah, it was mostly just circles. I would say, that was like, kind of
Ana Chkhaidze: like, I was kind of like seeing. The only pattern I saw was the squiggly lines like down the screen. And there were like multiple of them just covering the screen. It was for a split second, but mostly I saw, like a lot of circles. Either it was like circles made of spir, or like a spiral made us made out of circles and just spinning around, or it was like a circle, just like pulsating like
Ana Chkhaidze: gradually like pulsating up and like becoming a bigger circle. But yeah, I noticed like, it was like when my eyes were like not focusing on the screen. It was when I'd see these patterns. But when I would like snap back into reality like everything's gone, and it's just like a red screen flashing at me.
Ana Chkhaidze: Can you.